Based on the chilling true story.
The Order is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by Justin Kurzel.
A string of violent robberies in the Pacific Northwest leads veteran FBI agent Terry
Husk into a white supremacist plot to overthrow the federal government.
Terry Husk, played by Jude Law.
Robert Jay Mathews, played by Nicholas Hoult.
Jamie Bowen, played by Tye Sheridan.
Joanne Carney, played by Jurnee Smollett.
Debbie Mathews, played by Alison Oliver.
Zillah Craig, played by Odessa Young.
The Order is a 2024 crime thriller film directed by Justin Kurzel and written by Zach Baylin, based
on the 1989 non-fiction book The Silent Brotherhood by Kevin Flynn and Gary Gerhardt.
The film revolves around an FBI agent who goes after a white supremacist terrorist group
known as the Order that was active in the United States in the 1980s.
It stars Jude Law as  FBI agent Terry Husk and Nicholas Hoult
as Robert Jay Mathews, leader of The Order.
Tye Sheridan, Jurnee Smollett, Alison Oliver, and
Marc Maron appear in supporting roles.
The film had its world premiere at the 81st Venice International Film
Festival on August 31, 2024, where it competed for the Golden Lion.
It received a limited theatrical release in the United States on December 6, 2024, and
was released worldwide on the streaming platform Amazon Prime Video.
It received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
fbi, idaho, based on true story, heist.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.